<ROSETTASCRIPTS>

  <SCOREFXNS>
    # Full Atom-level score function is used to repack disulfides in NubInitio
    # and guide FastDesign.
    <ScoreFunction name="fullatom" weights="talaris2014" />
  </SCOREFXNS>

  <RESIDUE_SELECTORS>
    # Standard FFL ResidueSelectors.
    <xi:include href="xml_pieces/selectors.xml" />

    # TEMPLATE POSE:
    #   The one that will be used as guide to refold the protein.
    #   One needs to define the region from that protein that will be
    #   substituted by the MOTIF of interes. We call that region INSERTION.
    <Index name="insertion"  resnums="72A-79A" />
    <Not   name="!insertion" selector="insertion" />

    #   The template pose can only contain ONE SINGLE CHAIN. This is needed
    #   both for StructFragmentMover and NubInitioMover. This is due to the
    #   fact that fragment creation and usage in the ab initio protocol will
    #   generate unexpected behaviours when called upon multiple chains.
    <Chain name="templateChain"  chains="A" />
    <Not   name="!templateChain" selector="templateChain" />

    #   When MOTIF has a DIFFERENT SIZE than the insertion, this translates
    #   into a size change of the design with respect to the template. As
    #   RMSD evaluation requires same-sized proteins, we need to create a
    #   selector that will only select as much as we can compare.
    <And name="templateChain!insert" selectors="templateChain,!insertion" />

    # MOTIF POSE:
    #   We need to select the residues from the motif pose that we actually
    #   consider our QUERY MOTIF and what we consider our BINDERS.
    <Index name="query_motif" resnums="255P-276P" />
    <Index name="heavy_chain" resnums="1H-111H" />
    <Index name="light_chain" resnums="1L-108L" />
    <Or    name="antibody"    selectors="heavy_chain,light_chain" />

    #   The design will keep the same chain name as the one of the query motif.
    #   This is done so that, if binders are also added, the chain naming will
    #   not overlap and also that it will be consistent with the source PDB.
    <Chain name="designChain" chains="P" />
  </RESIDUE_SELECTORS>

  <MOVE_MAP_FACTORIES>
    # Standard FFL MoveMap
    <xi:include href="xml_pieces/movemap.xml" />
  </MOVE_MAP_FACTORIES>

  <TASKOPERATIONS>
    # Standard FFL TaskOperators
    <xi:include href="xml_pieces/taskoperators.xml" />
  </TASKOPERATIONS>

  <FILTERS>
    # We will check the RMSD between the pose after NubInitioMover and at the end.
    <RmsdFromResidueSelectorFilter name="rmsd_drift" reference_name="refolded_pose"
      reference_selector="designChain" query_selector="designChain" confidence="0" />
    # We will check at the end the final RMSD between the template and the Design
    <RmsdFromResidueSelectorFilter name="final_rmsd" reference_name="template_pose"
      reference_selector="templateChain!insert" query_selector="TEMPLATE" confidence="0" />

    # Get the score of only the design chain, as the score of the binder will hide it.
    <ScorePoseSegmentFromResidueSelectorFilter name="design_score" confidence="0"
      residue_selector="designChain" />
  </FILTERS>

  <MOVERS>
    # EXTRA POSES TO SAVE/LOAD:
    #   We will SAVE the TEMPLATE (input pose) to measure the FINAL RMSD of the design.
    <SavePoseMover name="saveTemplate" restore_pose="0" reference_name="template_pose" />
    #   We will SAVE the REFOLDED POSE before the design process to evaluate the RMSD
    #   DRIFT between it and the final design.
    <SavePoseMover name="saveRefolded" restore_pose="0" reference_name="refolded_pose" />
    #   We will LOAD in parallel the MOTIF POSE from which the MOTIF (and BINDER, if any)
    #   will be obtained. Loading a PDB FILE into the DataMap does not require for this
    #   mover to be called in the PROTOCOL (actually, it should NOT be called).
    <SavePoseMover name="loadTarget" reference_name="target_pose" pdb_file="3ixt.pdb.gz" />

    # The TEMPLATE pose MUST BE A SINGLE, UNBROKEN CHAIN. This is non-negotiable.
    # Extra chains need to be deleted BEFORE starting to create FRAGMENTS.
    <DeleteRegionMover name="removeExtraChains" residue_selector="!templateChain" />

    # FRAGMENT CREATION/LOADING:
    # The creates the fragments (if they need to be created) or loads them from a file
    # into the DataMap with the "frags" identifier (that needs to be specified in the NubInitio).
    <StructFragmentMover name="FragmentPicker" prefix="frags" vall_file="database/vall.jul19.2011.gz"
      output_frag_files="1" small_frag_file="frags.200.3mers" large_frag_file="frags.200.9mers" />

    # Guiding the ab inito with CONSTRAINTS highly improves the results from NubInitioMover.
    <AddConstraints name="addCST" >
      <AtomPairConstraintGenerator name="atompairCST" sd="3.0" ca_only="true" min_seq_sep="6"
        use_harmonic="true" unweighted="true" max_distance="40" residue_selector="templateChain" />
    </AddConstraints>

    # After folding, we will remove the constraints so that the design process is not guided by
    # constraints that do not belong anymore to our design (they come from the original scaffold).
    <ClearConstraintsMover name="cleanCST" />

    # INSERTION AND REFOLDING
    #   For demonstrative purposes, some residues in the MOTIF are allowed to mutate.
    <NubInitioMover name="FFL" fragments_id="frags" template_motif_selector="insertion" fullatom_scorefxn="fullatom" >
      <Nub reference_name="target_pose" residue_selector="query_motif" binder_selector="antibody" >
        <Segment order="1" n_term_flex="2" c_term_flex="2" editable="3,5,7,9" />
      </Nub>
    </NubInitioMover>

    # This mover is very helpful in terms of showing the setup of the pose after the
    # NubInitioMover has been run.
    <DisplayPoseLabelsMover name="showDesign" />

    # SEQUENCE EDITING
    <FastDesign name="DesignRelax" scorefxn="fullatom" repeats="3"
      task_operations="FFLMOTIF_TASKOP,FFLFLEX_TASKOP,FFLTEMPLATE_TASKOP"
      delete_virtual_residues_after_FastRelax="true"
      movemap_factory="FFLSTANDARD_MOVEMAP" >
    </FastDesign>

    # This might be helpful in order to latter on analyse the designs in PyMOL
    <ResidueLabelsToPymolSelectionMover name="pymolselect" pdb_count="true" />
  </MOVERS>

  <APPLY_TO_POSE>
  </APPLY_TO_POSE>

  <PROTOCOLS>
    # Preparing Template
    <Add mover="removeExtraChains" />
    <Add mover="saveTemplate" />
    <Add mover="FragmentPicker" />
    <Add mover="addCST" />
    # Fold
    <Add mover="FFL" />
    <Add mover="saveRefolded" />
    <Add mover="showDesign" />
    # Design
    <Add mover="cleanCST" />
    <Add mover="DesignRelax" />
    # Evaluate
    <Add filter="rmsd_drift" />
    <Add filter="final_rmsd" />
    <Add filter="design_score" />
    <Add mover="pymolselect" />
  </PROTOCOLS>
  <OUTPUT />
</ROSETTASCRIPTS>
